<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on News</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on News</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Book Suggestions by Berenice Lui</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/book-suggestions-by-berenice-lui/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/book-suggestions-by-berenice-lui/</guid>
      <description>On April 9, I put a question in the chat asking what book suggestions you guys have. I will be going over 5 books suggested by order of the time it was posted.
 Yabin suggested the series Steve the Noob! According to google, Steve the Noob is a 46 book nonofficial Minecraft series. The author is Steve, no full name is given. Anushka said the series Boxcar Children! The Boxcar Children series has over 166 books and comes out with more every year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math by Ira Tiwary</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/math-by-ira-tiwary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/math-by-ira-tiwary/</guid>
      <description>As you know, we’re in our 6th unit of math. Recently, we have studied parentheses in equations, unneeded information, and two step problems. For a review, try this problem! Jackie, Jake, James, Jacob and Jane all saved specific amounts of money. Jane had $24. Jackie had $5.78 more than Jake. Jake had 2 times as much as James. James had $2.17 less than Jacob. Jacob had $18.39. How much money did Jackie have?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Trail by Ira Tiwary</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/oregon-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/oregon-trail/</guid>
      <description>As you know, we have been on the Oregon Trail for 46 days, and we are right now in the middle of current day Nebraska. Our journey had been uneventful but one frightful day, a thunderstorm occurs!
Lightning flashes, clouds rumble, and rain pounds down. The dirt trail turns sloshy, and one wagon turns over! The poor Websters lose all their food!
Luckily, we are only nine days away from the nearest trading point, Fort Laramie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTA Updates by Angela Johnson</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/pta-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/pta-updates/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoutouts</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/shoutouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/shoutouts/</guid>
      <description>Happy Birthday to Natalie. Congratulation to Berenice for showing Perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stand Up Yumi Chung by Silvia</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/stand-up-yumi-chung/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/stand-up-yumi-chung/</guid>
      <description>We picked a new book a few weeks ago. It is called ‘Stand up, Yumi Chung!’ It is about a girl named Yumi. She has a mother, father, and a sister. She wants to pursue a comedy career, but her sister is the only one that supports her inside of her family.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
